120 is our buy opinion and we want to buy
SSC Loot on which we have our house rent.
This stop has been coming for a long time, for about one and a half to two months,
we have been seeing consolidation in it and now
we feel that it is fully ready for the
next issue, but it is
sitting at an inch above for medium to long term, so let's
complete the heavy buying on Loot for medium term and long term, after all
these technical sachar are
turning in good condition and the special thing is
margin and safety and the targets are quite high,
so here we are
giving player's opinion for two targets, the first target is
1750, the
first target is 1750, the second
target is 1999, for both these targets,
ICICI Lombard is on this side and
buying on decline, do that,
buy opinion is coming for such a body that
for you, from Punaji and Rakesh
ji, at this time keep this gap for 6 to 12 minutes